          {
            "partNo": "one",
            "subtitle": "Details of the listed entity",
            "questions": [
              {
                "questionNo": "1",
                "question": "Corporate Identity Number (CIN) of the Listed Entity",
                "questionOptions": [],
                "questionAnswer":  json_merge["Corporate Identity Number (CIN) of the Listed Entity"]
              },
              {
                "questionNo": "2",
                "question": "Name of the Listed Entity",
                "questionOptions": [],
                "questionAnswer":  json_merge["Name of the Listed Entity"]
              },
              {
                "questionNo": "3",
                "question": "Year of incorporation",
                "questionOptions": [],
                "questionAnswer":  json_merge["Year of incorporation"]
              },
              {
                "questionNo": "4",
                "question": "Registered office address",
                "questionOptions": [],
                "questionAnswer":  json_merge["Registered office address"]
              },
              {
                "questionNo": "5",
                "question": "Corporate address",
                "questionOptions": [],
                "questionAnswer":  json_merge["Corporate address"]
              },
              {
                "questionNo": "6",
                "question": "Email",
                "questionOptions": [],
                "questionAnswer":  json_merge["Email"]
              },
              {
                "questionNo": "7",
                "question": "Telephone",
                "questionOptions": [],
                "questionAnswer":  json_merge["Telephone"]
              },
              {
                "questionNo": "8",
                "question": "Website",
                "questionOptions": [],
                "questionAnswer":  json_merge["Website"]
              },
              {
                "questionNo": "9",
                "question": "Financial year for which reporting is being done",
                "questionOptions": [],
                "questionAnswer":  json_merge["Financial year for which reporting is being done"]
              },
              {
                "questionNo": "10",
                "question": "Name of the Stock Exchange(s) where shares are listed",
                "questionOptions": [],
                "questionAnswer":  json_merge["Name of the Stock Exchange(s) where shares are listed"]
              },
              {
                "questionNo": "11",
                "question": "Paid-up Capital",
                "questionOptions": [],
                "questionAnswer":  json_merge["Paid-up Capital"]
              },
              {
                "questionNo": "12",
                "question": "Name and contact details of the person who may be contacted",
                "questionOptions": [],
                "questionAnswer":  json_merge["Name and contact details"]
              },
              {
                "questionNo": "13",
                "question": "Reporting boundary - Are the disclosures under this report made on a standalone basis (i.e. only for the entity) or on a consolidated basis (i.e. for the entity and all the entities which form a part of its consolidated financial statements, taken together)",
                "questionOptions": [],
                "questionAnswer":  json_merge["Reporting boundary - Are the disclosures under this report made on a standalone basis (i.e. only for the entity) or on a consolidated basis (i.e. for the entity and all the entities which form a part of its consolidated financial statements, taken together)"]
              },
              {
                "questionNo": "14",
                "question": "Name of assurance provider",
                "questionOptions": [],
                "questionAnswer":  json_merge["Name of assurance provider"]
              },
              {
                "questionNo": "15",
                "question": "Type of assurance obtained",
                "questionOptions": [],
                "questionAnswer":  json_merge["Type of assurance obtained"]
              }
            ]
          },


